RG 166:004, Connecticut Tercentenary Pamphlet Collection
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut Tercentenary Pamphlet Collectin
1934-1935
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut State Library (collector)
.5 cubic feet
Connecticut tercentenary celebrations by the various towns of the state. Includes programs, bulletins, and exhibit catalogs and other ephemera.
RG166_004
2011-073
Scope and Content
Programs and other ephemera for various town commemorations and celebrations including pageants, concerts, religious services, dinners, parades, dedications, and graduations.
Arrangement
Items from the Tercentenary Commission of the State of Connecticut are followed by items from various towns arranged alphabetically.
Related Material
, Connecticut State Library.
, Connecticut State Library.
RG 012, Records of the Connecticut State Library, Box 73, Tercentenary Commission, 1935 - 1936.
, Connecticut State Library.
, Connecticut State Library.
RG 064, Picture Group 360, Connecticut Tercentenary Celebration, 1935.
RG 169, Clubs and Private Organizations, Accession 2001-077, Wethersfield Tercentenary Committee, 1929-1934.
The book collections contain various materials published by the Commission or by others in connection with the Tercentenary observance. Included are the
Report to the Governor, 1936 June 30,
and the sixty "Historical Publications Series" pamphlets.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Tercentenary Commission of the State of Connecticut
Subjects:
Connecticut -- Centennial celebrations, etc
Document Types:
Admission tickets; Bulletins; Commercial directories; Exhibition catalogs; Guidebooks; Invitations; Programs (documents); Scripts (documents)
Restrictions on Access
See the policy.
Provenance
The records were transferred to the State Archives from the general collection in 2011. Formerly cataloged as 974.6 C763t to.
Container List
- Collection, 1934-1935
  - Connecticut Tercentenary Bulletin, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Tercentenary Commission of the State of Connecticut, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ansonia - Durham, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Includes items for: Ansonia, Berlin, Bloomfield, Branford, Bridgeport, Bristol, Canaan-North Canaan, Chaplin, Cheshire, Clinton, Colchester, Colebrook, Cornwall-Kent-Sherman, Durham.
  - East Granby - Farmington, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Includes items for: East Granby, East Haddam, East Hartford, East Haven, East Lyme, Ellington, Enfield, Fairfield, Farmington.
  - Glastonbury - Litchfield, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Includes items for: Glastonbury, Granby, Greenwich, Groton, Guilford, Hamden, Hartford, Hebron, Killingworth-Clinton, Lisbon, Lebanon, Litchfield.
  - Madison - Norwich, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Includes items for: Madison, Middlefield, Middletown, Mystic, Naugatuck, New Britain, New Canaan, New Haven, New London, Newtown, Noank, Norfolk, North Branford, Norwalk, Norwich.
  - Orange - Ridgefield, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Includes items for: Orange, Oxford, Plainville, Plymouth, Portland, Prospect, Redding, Ridgefield.
  - Salem - Suffield, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Includes items for: Salem, Saugatuck, Saybrook, Seymour, Simsbury, Southington, Stamford, Storrs, Stonington, Stratfield, Stratford, Suffield.
  - Thomaston - Woodstock, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Includes items for: Thomaston, Torrington, Vernon, Waterbury, Westport, Wethersfield, Wilton, Winchester, Windsor Locks, Woodbridge, Woodstock.